<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<cheatsheet title="Layer Style">
  <intro href="/net.refractions.udig.help/EN/Change a Layers Style.html">
    <description>
    	In this cheat sheet we are going to learn how to change the style of a layer.
	</description>
  </intro>  
  
  <item skip="false" title="Open Style Editor" dialog="true" href="/net.refractions.udig.help/EN/Style Editor Dialog.html">
     <description>
    The style of a layer may be changed by opening the Style Editor.
    <br/><br/> 
	Open up the Style Editor dialog by <b>Right Clicking</b> on the layer you wish to style and choosing <b>Change Style</b>.
	<br/><br/> 
	<b>Example:</b> In the layer view <b>Right click</b> on the layer "countries" and select <b>Change Style</b>
	</description>
  </item>
 
  <item
        title="Change Style" >
     <description>
       Change the layers fill colour by selection the <b>Fill</b> tab then click on the colour button to activate the colour dialog.
<br/><br/>
Select a new colour and close the dialog.
     </description>
  </item>
  
  <item
        title="Apply">
     <description>
        Click the <b>Apply</b> button to see what this new style looks like on your Map. The Layer view will also be updated to reflect the current style
     </description>
  </item> 
  
   <item
        title="Ok">
     <description>
        Click the <b>Ok</b> button if you are happy with your new style.
     </description>
  </item> 
  
  <item
        title="XML"
        href="/net.refractions.udig.help/EN/Style Layer Descriptor.html">
     <description>
       Should you need to do something a little more complex than what the simple or theme pages offer, the XML page allows you to directly modify the Styled Layer Descriptor document (this describes how you would like your layer drawn).
     </description>
  </item> 
  
   <item
    title="Style View">
     <description>
      uDig also offers a Style View that can be utilised to perform simple layer styling. To see the Style View in action change to the Style Perspective by selecting  <b>Window > Open Perspective > Style Perspective</b>
      </description>
     <command serialization="org.eclipse.ui.perspectives.showPerspective(org.eclipse.ui.perspectives.showPerspective.perspectiveId=net.refractions.udig.ui.stylePerspective)" required="false" translate=""/>
  </item> 
</cheatsheet>