<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<compositeCheatsheet name="Quickstart">
    <taskGroup name= "Quickstart">
        <intro> 
This is a quick introduction to the uDig application included as part of online help.
<br/><br/>
Before you start please take a moment to download some sample data that we have made available on the web. <a href="http://udig.refractions.net/download/">http://udig.refractions.net/download/</a>
<br/><br/>
When asked for the file location choose an appropriate location such as your desktop unzip the contents of this file into a data folder
        </intro>
         
         <onCompletion>Congratulations you have completed the Quickstart.</onCompletion>  
                    
         <task kind="cheatsheet" name= "Workbench" skip="true">
              <param name = "id" value = "net.refractions.udig.help.cheatsheet.workbench" />
              <intro>This Cheat Sheet will introduce you to the basic layout of the Workbench. If you are already familiar with the Workbench layout you can skip this task.
              </intro>
               <onCompletion>Congratulations you now know about the Workbenck layout.</onCompletion>                  
         </task>
         
         <task kind="cheatsheet" name= "Project" skip="true">
              <param name="id" value="net.refractions.udig.help.cheatsheet.newprojectwizard" />
              <intro>
              This cheat sheet introduce you to Projects.
              <br/><br/>
              Projects can be automatically created as part of Add Layer and Add Map. This cheat sheet focuses on manually creating a project.
              </intro>
               <onCompletion>Congratulations you now know about Projects.</onCompletion>                  
         </task>
         
         <taskGroup name= "Add Layers" kind = "sequence">
             <intro> First you will learn how to add some simple layers to our map. 
             <br/><br/>This task requires that you have some sample data, you can download the latest sample 
             data set from the <a href="http://udig.refractions.net/download/">uDig website download page</a>.
             </intro>
              <onCompletion>Congratulations you have added additional layers to uDig.</onCompletion>
             <task kind="cheatsheet" name="Add Layers" id="addLayers">
                 <intro>
                 	This cheat sheet walks you through the process of adding a shape file to uDig.
                 </intro>
                 <param name="id" value = "net.refractions.udig.help.cheatsheet.loadShapeFile"/>
                 <onCompletion>Congratulations you have succeeded added a shape file.</onCompletion>
             </task>
             <task kind="cheatsheet" name= "Drag in Layer">
                 <intro>
					In addition to using the using the dialog tool you can also drag content onto your uDig workbench and uDig will
					do all the work for you.
					
					This task will walk you through dragging a layer onto you map.
                 </intro>
                 <param name = "id" value = "net.refractions.udig.help.cheatsheet.dragFromFileSystem" />
                 <onCompletion>Congratulations you have succeeded dragging a layer onto your map.</onCompletion>           
             </task> 
             
             <task kind="cheatsheet" name= "Web Map Service">
                 <intro>
					This section covers the use of Web Map Servers, which make available layers of information that can be added to your map.
                 </intro>
                 <param name = "id" value = "net.refractions.udig.help.cheatsheet.webmapservice" />
                 <onCompletion>Congratulations you have succeeded added Web Map Services (WMS) to your map.</onCompletion>           
             </task>       
         </taskGroup>
         
         <taskGroup name= "Working With The Map" kind = "sequence">
             <intro>
             Now we have some layers on our map let's learn how to work with them.
             </intro>
              <onCompletion>Congratulations you now know how to work with the map.</onCompletion>
         <task kind="cheatsheet" name= "Layer Order" skip="true">
              <param name = "id" value = "net.refractions.udig.help.cheatsheet.layerorder" />
              <intro>In this cheat sheet we are going to order some of the layers we just added.
              </intro>
               <onCompletion>Congratulations you now know how to order layers.</onCompletion>                  
         </task>
         
         <task kind="cheatsheet" name= "Style Layer" skip="true">
              <param name = "id" value = "net.refractions.udig.help.cheatsheet.stylelayer" />
              <intro>In this cheat sheet we are going to apply some simple styles to a layer.
              </intro>
               <onCompletion>Congratulations you now know how to style a layer.</onCompletion>                  
         </task>
         
         <task kind="cheatsheet" name= "Map Navigation" skip="true">
              <param name = "id" value = "net.refractions.udig.help.cheatsheet.mapnavigation" />
              <intro>
              In this cheat sheet we are going to learn about using some of the tools available to navigate around the map.
              </intro>
               <onCompletion>Congratulations you now know how to navigate around a map.</onCompletion>                  
         </task>
         </taskGroup>
    </taskGroup>
</compositeCheatsheet> 