<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<cheatsheet title="Map Navigation">
  <intro href="/net.refractions.udig.help/EN/Navigation Tools.html">
    <description>
    	You can control where the Map Editor is looking by using the navigation tools. The 
    	navigation tools are located in the tool bar along the top of the screen.
	</description>
  </intro>  

  <item title="Zoom Tool">
     <description>
		The <b>Zoom Tool</b> is available by default. You can activate the tool by clicking 
		it in the tool bar.
	</description>
	<command 
		serialization="net.refractions.udig.tools.ZoomCommand" 
		required="false"/>
  </item>
  
  <item title="Zoom In Selection">
     <description>
		Use the <b>Zoom Tool</b> by drawing a box, using the left mouse button, around the area of the 
		map you wish to see.
	</description>
  </item>
  
  <item title="Zoom Out Selection">
     <description>
		To <b>Zoom Out</b> draw a box with the right mouse button. The current map will be 
		located within the box you draw.
	</description>
  </item>
  
  <item title="Zoom In">
     <description>
		 The <b>Zoom In Tool</b> can be used to change the scale by a fixed amount. Clicking the tool once will 
		 zoom the map in one level, clicking it again will zoom the map out a further level.
	</description>
	 <command 
		serialization="net.refractions.udig.tool.default.zoom.in" 
		required="false"/>
  </item>
  
  <item title="Zoom Out">
     <description>
		The <b>Zoom Out Tool</b> can be used to change the scale by a fixed amount. Clicking the tool once will 
		 zoom out the map by one level, clicking in again will zoom the map out a further level.
	</description>
	<command 
		serialization="net.refractions.udig.tool.default.zoom.out" 
		required="false"/>
  </item>
  
  <item title="Zoom To Extent">
     <description>
		The <b>Show All Tool</b> can be used to return the map to its full size at any time. Click the tool once
		to zoom to the full extent.
	</description>
	<command 
		serialization="net.refractions.udig.tool.default.zoom.all" 
		required="false"/>
  </item>
  
  <item title="Pan Tool">
     <description>
		The <b>Pan Tool</b> can be used to scroll around your map with out changing the scale. You can activate the tool by clicking 
		it in the tool bar.
	</description>
  <command 
		serialization="net.refractions.udig.tools.PanCommand" 
		required="false"/>
  </item>
  
  <item title="Pan Map">
     <description>
		Using the left mouse button <b>Click and Drag</b> the map to pan out the area you wish to view.
	</description>
	<command 
		serialization="net.refractions.udig.tools.panLeftCommand" 
		required="false"/>
  </item>

</cheatsheet>